In medical research, evidence is the foundation.
MedEvidence AI — Your intelligent evidence-based medicine search assistant.
Clinical decisions require evidence-based support.
But facing massive medical literature, have you ever wondered —
How to classify evidence levels?
How to quickly search Chinese and English literature?
Where are the high-quality studies?
MedEvidence AI, powered by KnowS evidence-based database
and StepFun large language model, provides you with
Bilingual intelligent literature search,
5-level evidence grading,
and one-stop AI-generated clinical summaries.
Let's try a Chinese search.
Enter "Meta分析 抗生素" (Meta-analysis antibiotics),
the system automatically calls the Chinese literature database,
returning the most relevant research results.
As you can see, all 5 results are accurately identified as Level 1
— Meta-analysis or systematic review,
the highest level of evidence in evidence-based medicine.
No more manual study type classification —
the system does it for you.
English search is equally precise.
Search "COVID-19 vaccine randomized trial",
the system returns multiple high-quality RCTs,
all marked as Level 1.
Each paper includes journal name, impact factor,
DOI, publication date, and more,
helping you quickly assess quality and access the full text.
What is the 5-level evidence grading system?
From Level 5: case reports and expert opinions,
to Level 4: case series and clinical guidelines,
Level 3: cohort and case-control studies,
then Level 2: lower-quality randomized controlled trials,
and the highest Level 1
— Meta-analysis and high-quality RCTs.
Higher evidence level means more reliable results.
Technically, MedEvidence AI is built on FastAPI,
deeply integrated with KnowS evidence-based database
and StepFun large language model.
Supports one-click deployment on ModelScope,
Docker container deployment,
and local execution — fully open source.
We prioritize medical safety and compliance.
This tool does not use real patient data,
does not provide diagnostic advice,
and is for medical research and learning only.
Please follow medical advice for clinical decisions.
MedEvidence AI,
illuminating every corner of medical research with AI.
Try it now and start your intelligent evidence journey.